George and Ira Gershwin Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-63)
  - Music from Shows (Box 1-47)
    - Pardon my English [1933] (Box 19-27)
      - Finaletto, Act II scene IV
        - Robert Russell Bennett holograph manuscript full score; 32 p. (Box-folder 19/23)
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; 15 p. ea., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 19/24)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 19/24)
      - Freud and Jung and Adler
        - William Daly holograph manuscript full score; 11 p. (Box-folder 20/1)
        - William Daly holograph manuscript full score; [8] p., Additional section; Caption title: The doctors’ dance (Box-folder 20/2)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p., Refrain only, no lyric (Box-folder 20/3)
        - Photocopied manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p., Incomplete, refrain only (Box-folder 20/3)
        - Photocopied manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; 6 [i.e. 5] p. (Box-folder 20/3)
        - IG holograph/typescript/photocopied lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 20/3)
      - Golo theme
        - Adolph Deutsch holograph manuscript full score; 2 p. (Box-folder 20/4)
      - Hail the happy couple
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 20/5)
      - He's not himself
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [5] p. (Box-folder 20/6)
      - He's oversexed
        - Manuscript melody line; [2] p., Incomplete (Box-folder 20/7)
        - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; 2 p. (Box-folder 20/7)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 20/7)
      - In three-quarter time
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p. (Box-folder 20/8)
        - Robert Russell Bennett holograph manuscript full score; [54] p. (Box-folder 20/9)
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; 8 p. ea., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 20/10)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] p. (Box-folder 20/10)
        - Copyist manuscript SATB score arrangement; 1, 5 p. (Box-folder 20/10)
        - Copyist manuscript SATB score arrangement; 6 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 20/11)
        - Copyist manuscript vocal parts; [12] p. (Box-folder 20/11)
      - Invitation to the waltz (Something else again)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [2] p., Unidentified sketch material on p. [2] (Box-folder 20/12)
      - Isn't it a pity
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p., Verse only (Box-folder 20/13)
        - Robert Russell Bennett holograph manuscript full score; [1, 39] p. (Box-folder 20/14)
        - Albert Sirmay’s manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p. (Box-folder 20/15)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Refrain only (Box-folder 20/15)
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 20/15)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 20/15)
      - Isn't it a pity. Change over into den
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 20/16)
      - I've got to be there
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Lyric in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 20/17)
        - Adolph Deutsch holograph manuscript full score; [74] p. (Box-folder 20/18)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [10] p., GG holograph notations (Box-folder 20/19)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 7 p. (Box-folder 20/20)
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 20/20)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 20/20)
        - Manuscript TTBB arrangement sketch for men’s chorus; [1] p. (Box-folder 21/1)
        - Manuscript vocal parts; [4] p. (Box-folder 21/1)
      - Lead me to heaven tonight
        - GG holograph manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 21/2)
      - The lorelei
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., No lyric (Box-folder 21/3)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 8 p. (Box-folder 21/4)
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 21/4)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 21/4)
        - Manuscript TTBB score arrangement for men’s chorus; [1] p., “Michael theme” on verso (Box-folder 21/4)
        - Copyist manuscript conductor’s score and 8 vocal parts; [9] p. (Box-folder 21/5)
        - Manuscript SATB score arrangement; [1] p., Last 8 bars (Box-folder 21/6)
        - Copyist manuscript vocal parts; [6] p., Last 8 bars (Box-folder 21/6)
      - Luckiest boy in the world, Early title for "Luckiest man in the world," Box-Folder 21/7-14
      - Luckiest man in the world
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., No lyric (Box-folder 21/7)
        - Robert Russell Bennett holograph manuscript full score; 34 p. (Box-folder 21/8)
      - Luckiest man in the world. Incidental
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 21/9)
      - Luckiest man in the world. Introduction
        - Manuscript piano sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 21/10)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 21/11)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p., Verse only, no lyric (Box-folder 21/12)
        - Robert Russell Bennett holograph manuscript full score; 59 p. (Box-folder 21/13)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in hand of Albert Sirmay; 6 p. (Box-folder 21/14)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in hand of Albert Sirmay; 7 p. (Box-folder 21/14)
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 21/14)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [11] p. (Box-folder 21/14)
      - Michael theme
        - Adolph Deutsch holograph manuscript full score; 2 p. (Box-folder 21/15)
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 21/16)
      - My cousin in Milwaukee
        - Adolph Deutsch holograph manuscript full score; [1, 26] p. (Box-folder 21/17)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 9 p. (Box-folder 21/18)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p. (Box-folder 21/18)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 21/18)
      - My cousin in Milwaukee. Change music into cafe scene
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 21/20)
      - My cousin in Milwaukee. Segue to So what?
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 21/21)
      - Nurses
        - Robert Russell Bennett holograph manuscript full score; [27] p. (Box-folder 21/22)
      - Nurses' entrance
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p. (Box-folder 21/23)
      - Opening, Act II
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [27] p., GG holograph emendations; Introduction to "I’ve got to be there," Box-Folder 20/17-21/1 on p. [27] (Box-folder 21/24)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of William Daly; 14 p., GG holograph emendations; No lyric (Box-folder 22/1)
        - Copyist manuscript SATB score arrangement; [1] p., Incomplete (Box-folder 22/2)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] p. (Box-folder 22/2)
      - Overture
        - GG holograph manuscript sketch; 2 p. (Box-folder 22/3)
        - William Daly holograph manuscript full score; 20 p. (Box-folder 22/4)
        - Copyist manuscript conductor’s lead sheet; 4 p. (Box-folder 22/5)
      - Pardon my English
        - William Daly holograph manuscript full score; 1, 20 p. (Box-folder 22/6)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 22/7)
      - Poor Michael! Poor Golo!, Alternate title for "He's not himself," Box-Folder 20/6
      - Randall's dance
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 22/8)
      - Schuhplader burlesque
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p., Caption title: "Schuplattler burlesque" (Box-folder 22/9)
      - Schuhplader dance
        - Copyist manuscript piano part; [2] p., Emendations in an unidentified hand; Caption title: "Schuh plattler dance" (Box-folder 22/10)
        - Photocopied manuscript piano-vocal sketch; [1] p., Caption title: "Shoe plattler’s dance" (Box-folder 22/10)
      - So what?
        - Robert Russell Bennett holograph manuscript full score; [1, 62] p. (Box-folder 22/11)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 8 p. (Box-folder 22/12)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of William Daly; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 22/12)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 22/12)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 22/12)
        - Copyist manuscript TTBB score arrangement for men’s chorus; [1] p. (Box-folder 22/13)
        - Copyist manuscript vocal parts; [9] p., Interlinear text in pencil (Box-folder 22/13)
      - So what? Incidental
        - 2 manuscript melody line sketches; [1] p. ea. (Box-folder 22/14)
      - Three-quarter time, Alternate title for "In three-quarter time," Box-Folder 20/8-11
      - Together at last
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 22/15)
        - William Daly holograph manuscript full score; 19 p. (Box-folder 22/16)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 7 p. (Box-folder 22/17)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 22/17)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 2] p., Lyric fragment (Box-folder 22/18)
        - Manuscript leadsheet in the hand of Michael Feinstein; [1] p., Refrain only (Box-folder 22/18)
        - Photocopied manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p., Lyric in ink (Box-folder 22/18)
        - Typescript/photocopied lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 22/18)
      - Tonight!
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 22/19)
      - Waltz
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 22/20)
      - Waltz sequence
        - GG holograph manuscript short score; [3-5] p., Incomplete (Box-folder 22/21)
      - Two waltzes in C
        - Copyist manuscript piano score; 8 p., Adapted by Saul Chaplin; In caption: Originally written ... for a musical sequence (but not used) ... (Box-folder 22/22)
      - Viennese sextet, Alternate title for linked numbers "Freud and Jung and Adler," Box-Folder 20/1-3 and "He's oversexed," Box-Folder 20/7
      - Watch your head
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 22/23)
      - What sort of wedding is this?
        - William Daly manuscript full score; [49] p. (Box-folder 22/24)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 8 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 23/1)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] p. (Box-folder 23/1)
      - Where you go, I go
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 23/2)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 5 p. (Box-folder 23/3)
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 23/3)
        - Manuscript sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 23/3)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 23/3)
      - Orchestral parts, Copyist manuscripts; Emendations in an unidentified hand; Laid in: Typescript notes
        - Oboe / English horn (Box-folder 23/4)
        - Alto saxophone I / clarinet I / baritone saxophone (Box-folder 23/5)
        - Alto saxophone II / flute / piccolo / clarinet II / alto saxophone III / clarinet III (Box-folder 23/6)
        - Tenor saxophone / clarinet II (Box-folder 23/7)
        - Horn I & II (Box-folder 24/1)
        - Trumpet I & II (Box-folder 24/2)
        - Trombone (Box-folder 24/3)
        - Drums (Box-folder 24/4)
        - Piano (Box-folder 25/1)
        - 1st violin I (Box-folder 25/2)
        - 1st violin II (Box-folder 25/3)
        - 1st violin III (Box-folder 26/1)
        - 1st violin IV (Box-folder 26/2)
        - 2nd violin (Box-folder 26/3)
        - Viola (Box-folder 26/4)
        - Violincello (Box-folder 27/1)
        - Double bass (Box-folder 27/2)
        - Viola II (cut from show) (Box-folder 27/3)
      - List of musical numbers
        - Manuscript; [2] p. (Box-folder 27/4)
      - Miscellaneous materials found with piano-vocal scores
        - 3 folders with manuscript notations and list of printed piano parts (Box-folder 27/5)
      - Scriptbook
        - Photocopied typescript manuscript [73] p., 1 of 2 (Box-folder 27/6)
        - Photocopied typescript manuscript [67] p., 2 of 2 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - Park Avenue [1946] (Box 28)
      - The dew was on the rose
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p. (Box-folder 28/1)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [14] p. (Box-folder 28/1)
      - The dew was on the rose. Interlude
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 2 p. (Box-folder 28/2)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 28/2)
      - The dew was on the rose. Reprise
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [9] p. (Box-folder 28/3)
      - Dinner song
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [5] p. (Box-folder 28/4)
      - Don't be a woman if you can
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 15 p. (Box-folder 28/5)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [20] p. (Box-folder 28/5)
      - For the life of me
        - IG holograph/typescript/photocopied lyric sheets; [16] p. (Box-folder 28/6)
      - The future Mrs. Coleman, See also "Stay as we are," Box-Folder 28/15
        - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [1] p., In caption: Thanks, Kay (Box-folder 28/7)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [5] p. (Box-folder 28/8)
      - Good-bye to all that
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [7] p. (Box-folder 28/9)
      - Heavenly day
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [5] p. (Box-folder 28/10)
      - Hope for the best
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [13] p. (Box-folder 28/11)
      - Land of opportunitee [sic]
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 10 p. (Box-folder 28/12)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [17] p. (Box-folder 28/12)
      - My son-in-law
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 28/13)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [20] p. (Box-folder 28/13)
      - Remind me not to leave town
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [12] p. (Box-folder 28/14)
      - Stay as we are
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p., In caption: New verse (Box-folder 28/15)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [8] p., p. [2]: The future Mrs. Coleman (unfinished) (Box-folder 28/15)
      - Sweet Nevada [waltz version]
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 8 p. (Box-folder 28/16)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [14] p. (Box-folder 28/16)
      - Sweet Nevada [western version]
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [9] p. (Box-folder 28/17)
      - There's no holding me
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [16] p. (Box-folder 28/18)
      - There's no holding me (if I can keep on holding you), Alternate title for "Dance alone with you," Box-Folder 6/10-11
      - There's nothing like marriage for people
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 12 p. (Box-folder 28/19)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [9] p. (Box-folder 28/19)
      - Tomorrow is the time
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 8 p. (Box-folder 28/20)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 28/20)
      - We're better off the way we are
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [8] p. (Box-folder 28/21)
      - Outline
        - Typescript; [9] p., IG holograph emendations; Laid-in: George Kaufman typescript letter to IG, 1946 January (incomplete); Laid-in: IG typescript notes (Box-folder 28/22)
      - Unidentified lyrics
        - IG holograph lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 28/23)
    - Piccadilly to Broadway [1920] (Box 28)
      - Baby blues
        - Maurice B. DePakh holograph manuscript full score; [1] p., Incomplete (Box-folder 28/24)
      - Bambino
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 28/25)
      - Gondolier, See "Bambino," Box-Folder 28/25
      - Mr. and Mrs.
        - Manuscript/typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 28/26)
      - On the brim of her old-fashioned bonnet
        - Maurice B. DePakh holograph manuscript full score; 23 p. (Box-folder 28/27)
      - Piccadilly's not a bit like Broadway
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 28/28)
      - Pick yo' partner
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 28/29)
      - Somehow I knew
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 28/30)
      - Something peculiar
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., Caption title: Spanish number (Box-folder 28/31)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., No lyric (Box-folder 28/31)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 28/31)
      - Who's who with you?, See "Who's who with you?" from Two little girls in blue, Box-Folder 46/40
    - Pins and needles [1922] (Box 28)
      - The Piccadilly walk
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 28/32)
    - Porgy and Bess [1935] (Box 29-30)
      - Act I, scene 1 [Opening]
        - Piano-vocal score proof copy; 1 p. (Box-folder 29/1)
      - Bess, you is my woman now
        - Photocopied sheet music (Spanish version) (Box-folder 29/2)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 29/2)
      - I got plenty o' nuthin'
        - Photocopied sheet music (Spanish version) (Box-folder 29/3)
        - Dubose Heyward original typescript lyric sheets; [2] p., GG holograph p. [1]; IG holograph p. [2] (Box-folder 29/3)
      - I hates yo' struttin' style
        - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [2] p., In caption: Maria (Box-folder 29/4)
      - It ain't necessarily so
        - Photocopied sheet music (Spanish version) (Box-folder 29/5)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [15] p., Laid-in: Typescript letter from IG to Alexander Smallens, 1941 December 15; Laid-in: Typescript letter from Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. to Larry Spier, 1949 March 28 (Box-folder 29/5)
        - IG typescript lyric sheet [1] p., 1952 revision for Adlai Stevenson (Box-folder 29/5)
      - Lonely boy
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p., No lyric (Box-folder 29/6)
        - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 29/7)
        - Dubose Heyward original typescript lyric sheet; [1] p., GG holograph addition (Box-folder 29/7)
        - IG holograph lyric sheet; [2] p., GG holograph names (Box-folder 29/7)
      - My man's gone now
        - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p., In caption: Serena song (Box-folder 29/8)
      - Oh, heav'nly Father
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 29/9)
      - Oh, I can't sit down!
        - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p., In caption: Picnic band (Box-folder 29/10)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 29/11)
      - Oh Lawd, I'm on my way
        - GG holograph manuscript sketch with drawings; [1] p. (Box-folder 29/12)
      - Oh, the train is at the station/Leaving for the Promis' Lan'
        - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [4] p. (Box-folder OV-1/5)
      - Prelude
        - GG holograph short score sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder OV-1/6)
      - A red-headed woman
        - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [2] p., Caption title: Crown blues (Box-folder 29/13)
      - Roll dem bones
        - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; 2 p., Laid in: GG signature; Gift of IG, 1939 May 24 (Box-folder 29/14)
      - Six prayers, Alternate title for "Oh, heav'nly Father," Box-Folder 29/9
      - Summertime
        - Photocopied sheet music (French version) (Box-folder 29/15)
        - Photocopied sheet (Spanish version) (Box-folder 29/15)
      - Sure to go to heaven
        - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p., In caption in the hand of IG: First sketch (Box-folder 29/16)
        - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 29/17)
      - There's a boat dat's leavin' soon for New York
        - GG holograph manuscript leadsheet; [1] p., Caption title: Boat for New York (Box-folder 29/18)
      - They pass by singin'
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; 2 p. (Box-folder 29/19)
      - What you want wid Bess?
        - GG holograph manuscript sketches; [3] p. (Box-folder 29/20)
      - Sketches
        - Act I, scene 1, rehearsal no. 22-23
          - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p., In caption: Part of crap game music (Box-folder 29/21)
        - Act I, scene 1, rehearsal no. 34-35
          - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; [2] p., In caption: Jake (Box-folder 29/22)
        - Act I, scene 1, rehearsal no. 70-72
          - GG holograph manuscript short scores (A, B, C, D); 4 leaves, In caption in the hand of IG: Porgy’s theme; Gift of Ira Gershwin, 1969 (Box-folder 29/23)
        - Act I, scene 1, rehearsal no. 93-94
          - GG holograph manuscript short score (A); [1] p., In caption: Fugatta; From the estate of Kay Swift (Box-folder 29/24)
        - Act I, scene 1, rehearsal no. 99-100
          - GG holograph manuscript short scores (A, B, C, D); 4 leaves, From the estate of Kay Swift (Box-folder 29/25)
        - Act I, scene 1, rehearsal no. 126-129
          - GG holograph manuscript sketches, Caption titles: Intro to Fugue; Fugue (Box-folder OV-1/7)
        - Act I, scene 1, rehearsal no. 130-131
          - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [2] p., In caption: Fugue interlude (Box-folder 29/26)
        - Act I, scene 1, rehearsal no. 131
          - GG holograph manuscript sketch; 1 p. (Box-folder 29/27)
        - Act II, scene 2, rehearsal no. 163-168
          - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p., Laid in: GG check and photocopied IG holograph notes (Box-folder 29/28)
        - Act II, scene 1, rehearsal no. 6-8
          - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [2] p., In caption in the hand of IG: Fisherman music (Box-folder 29/29)
        - Act II, scene 2, rehearsal 131, unused
          - GG holograph manuscript sketches; [7] p., In captions: Kittiwah; Laid in: IG typescript note (Box-folder 29/30)
        - Act II, scene 2, rehearsal no. 131
          - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; [2] p., In caption: Kittiwah (Africana) (Box-folder 29/31)
        - Act II, scene 3, rehearsal no. 225
          - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p., Labeled: Storm (Box-folder 29/32)
        - Act III, scene 3, Opening
          - GG holograph manuscript note on development; [1] p. (Box-folder 29/33)
        - Act III, scene 3, rehearsal no. 156-162
          - GG holograph manuscript sketch; 7 p., In caption: Trio; Laid-in: IG letter and GG check (Box-folder 29/34)
        - Miscellaneous and unused sketches
          - GG holograph manuscript sketches; 4 leaves, Laid in: IG typescript note (Box-folder 29/35)
        - Miscellaneous motives
          - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p., Laid in: IG typescript note (Box-folder OV-1/8)
      - Bound Items
        - Act I, scene I
          - GG holograph piano-vocal score; [104] p., 1934 May 23 (Box-folder Bound)
        - Act I, scene II
          - GG holograph piano-vocal score; 75 p. (Box-folder Bound)
        - Act II
          - GG holograph piano-vocal score (Box-folder Bound)
        - Act III
          - GG holograph piano-vocal score; [139] p. (Box-folder Bound)
        - Act I
          - GG holograph orchestral score; [167] p., Act I, scene I in caption: Late 1934-1935 September 2 (Box-folder Bound)
        - Act II
          - GG holograph orchestral score; [242] p. (Box-folder Bound)
        - Act III